Good afternoon Hello From Ukraine, the
добрый день Здравствуйте Из Украины
city of Khmelnitsky And you are
город Хмельницкий А вы
Vladivostok,
Владивосток
this is almost Japan
это уже почти Япония
Manchuria Majulia
Маньчжурия маджулия
I will ask people from Russia how you feel
Я у людей из России спрошу как вы
about the war in Ukraine
относитесь к войне в Украине
I am very negative because I lived in the
Я очень негативно потому что я жил в
UK as an
Великобритании
economic worker,
хозяйственного работника
I left there on January 25 and on January 24 the
я уехал туда 25 января а 24 началась
war began and  just with the Ukrainians with whom
война и как раз с украинцами с которыми
we lived, in principle, there are not such feuds.
мы жили в принципе не такие распри
I understand that nothing is wrong,
Я понимаю что ничего не так
well, in principle, how would I understand
ну в принципе что как бы я понимаю
in general that how who is to blame,
вообще что как кто как виноват
but absolutely not you are absolutely already
но абсолютно же не Вы абсолютно уже
well because many say that you are
хорошо потому что многие говорят что вы
also there like  it’s my fault
тоже там как-то виноват
in general, it’s just that life is such a collapse and I
вообще просто жизнь это такой развал и я
don’t know. Well, here in Vladivostok, how
не знаю Ну вот у вас во Владивостоке как
people relate to this, for the most
люди относятся к этому в большинстве
part, they are very zombified. I can’t even with my mother.
своем очень зомбированный Я даже с мамой
even though it’s really throwing off on them, but
хоть на них прям реально скидывает но
most honestly, I’ll say this,
большинство честно скажу так
and that’s when our mobilization began.
и вот когда у нас началась мобилизация
I say it
Я говорю
turns out I have a sister, he was already
получается у меня есть сестра ему уже
named,
назвали
I just mom  I say to my mother that I’m saying
я маме просто своей говорю что я говорю
[ __ ] it I won’t go to
нахуй вообще не пойду я
alternative service at all I just
альтернативную службу вообще просто не
won’t go to a foreign land at all
пойду вообще на чужую землю
what’s most interesting
что самое интересное
My mom just thinks that the sisters
Моя мама просто думает то что вот сестры
called in And I’m such a deviant, that is,
призвали А я вот такой уклонист то есть
I even
я даже
know we have this
у нас знаете у нас есть этот канал
Zolkin channel  some mothers
золкин который видео с пленными делают
call their parents,
разговоры там звонят родителям некоторые
they just don’t get stupid at all,
мамы вот просто они вообще не одупляются
that is,
то есть происходит
it just happens
это просто
But because of what do you think this
А вот из-за чего по вашему такое
happened to people
случилось с людьми
There is a lot of Propaganda and you know that
Здесь большая Пропаганда и знаете что
in general, before all this, the
вообще до всего этого
popularization of Putin, no one in
популяризация Путина никто его в
principle  didn’t love him, no one ever
принципе не любил его никто никогда не
chose him, that is, the guys all had to come
выбирал то есть ребята все было прийти
to somehow it was chosen But after
на как-то это выбрано Но после того как
the war began and I don’t know some kind of direct
началась война и не знаю какая-то прям
all-encompassing direct such love all people
всеобъемлющая прям такая любовь все люди
really really
прям реально
drown I talk with my mother
топить Я с мамой разговариваем
all my life as if just  [ __ ] in the ass,
всю жизнь как будто просто ебали в жопу
I'm just not looking for just wider rolls,
просто я не ищу просто булки еще шире
just like that, I don't know
просто вот так вот я не знаю
Even those who were there, they pile on for
Даже те которые были там они навалить за
Russia, you
Россию
look if  I always say Russia
смотришь если я всегда говорю Россия
if it is such a rich country there is only
если она такая богатая страна там только
oil and gas this money is wasted why
нефти газа эти деньги деваются почему
is it the Czech Republic that there is no dough that
это Чехии которые нету бабла который
buys better than people
покупает лучше чем люди
Trained to get I
Поездил получить Я посмотрел на
looked at Scotland
Шотландию Как живет допустим Шотландия
it’s just built It’s so cool and by the
просто построен Это так круто а вы
way you were in Japan there
кстати в Японии были там
Japan
Японии были
was I had a visa I never went there
у меня была виза я так и не поехал туда
we can go here to
у нас здесь можно поехать именно
work for contract auto parts
работать на на контрактный автозапчасти
people from Vladivostok Japan are closer to
люди из Владивостока Японии ближе к
Japan China than in Moscow so I’m
Японии Китае чем в Москве так мне
wondering yes  how they saw the development of those
интересно да как они видели развитие тех
countries
стран
in general, I’ll tell you this, that is,
вообще я вам так скажу то есть в
basically Vladivostok, it’s like it’s generally
основном Владивосток он как бы он вообще
Vladivostok Khabarovsk, it’s generally a completely
Владивосток Хабаровск это вообще совсем
different system, you know how Khabarovsk is,
другая система знаете как Хабаровск это
damn it, it’s more there more some other kind of
блин это больше там больше какой-то еще
tea to smoke some 90 you know
всякие чай курить какие-то 90 знаете вот
this prevails so much it is more
такое преобладает столько он больше
such a capitalist more such a
такой капиталистичный более такой
progressive city
прогрессивный город
is somehow not at all interested in
вообще как-то не интересуется принципе
some kind of war policy. Here people
политикой войной какой-то Здесь люди
live apart. It seems to me that the
живут обособленно Мне кажется то что
Far East should simply move away
просто Дальний Восток должен отойти
after you are the winners.
после после того как вы победители
This should Siberia move away and the Far
Это должно Сибирь отойдет и Дальний
East should leave
Восток он вообще должен уйти Но как-то
altogether.
вообще а Москва
they are territorially connected with Moscow,
не связанные с Москвой они
in fact, yes.
территориально по сути да Если так это
we are somehow
общаться вообще как-то то есть мы как-то
slightly different from
немножко отличаемся
Vladivostok But somehow, in general, somehow
Владивостока Но как-то вообще как-то
a little bit differently, therefore, it seems to me
по-другому чуть-чуть поэтому мне кажется
yes And even more so for Russia to stand up,
да И тем более для России чтобы встать
if at all it is possible and in general to
если вообще это возможно и вообще хоть
somehow reconcile, the
как-то примириться
split is inevitable, this really
раскол неизбежен это правда
changes  I’ll see you out of
изменяет у вас из этого
this and the cars
провожу и тачки
so they’re all right here,
так они все права ровные здесь вообще
there’s no Russian production at all. When I
нету Российского производства Я когда
left in Yekaterinburg,
уехал в Екатеринбурге
that is, there’s a whole other world
То есть тут вообще Другой мир Ну как бы
.  you like cars for people
получается типа у вас как машины у людей
with a steering wheel on the right to drive as well as for a
с рулем справа на ездите как ну как для
vrulik yes like according to the rules
врулик да типа по правила
Well, yes, that is, I passed on the rights, I
Ну да то есть я-то сдавал на права я тут
get it here
получается
And even more so the car is called differently
И тем более машины называется по-другому
, let's say Mazda 3 we have Mazda axela
у вас допустим Mazda 3 у нас Mazda axela
you have a brain with a Mazda atenza, we have a Honda
у вас мозг с Mazda atenza у нас Honda
Fit, you have a Honda Jazz, that is,
Fit у вас Honda Jazz то есть
and cars from Japan will catch up with
а машины с Японии догонят
everything, getting closer all the
все-все
time, and this is happening Why is
постоянно так и происходит Почему здесь
the business here, as it were, well and working And
и бизнес такой как бы ну и работает И
in general, Vladivostok, as it were,
вообще как бы ну Владивосток он
when he lived in Great Britain  that is,
когда вот жил Великобритании то есть на
many Ukrainians at me That's it, they were
меня украинцы многие Вот именно
fooled by the fact that there was a
залупались то что
war and they said that, like, here you
война и говорили что типа вот вы должны
should gather some kind of rally there,
там собрать там какой-то митинг там
go out there and Damn, that's just what I
что-то выйти и Блин вот просто что я
can do, let's say I need to
могу сделать допустим Мне нужно
let's say this What do you think
допустим вот Как вы считаете
what I need  I think Look here it is necessary
что мне нужно я считаю Смотрите тут надо
to separate what happened on February 24 and what
разделять что было 24 февраля и что
is now, of course,
сейчас сейчас уже конечно ни на какой
no one will come out to any rally so easily. So on
митинг никто так просто не выйдет Так 24
February 24, people could still go out there with
февраля еще могли люди там выходили с
posters and so on now this is a
плакатами и так далее сейчас вот это
general silence But gave a background to that  that
общее молчание Но дала фон к тому что
no one will come out like that, so the
уже так никто не вылезет так уже
repressive machine is already working to its fullest, but
репрессивная машина работает на всю но
here the first thing that is needed is that it does not support
тут первое что надо это не поддерживает
because many say that I can do it,
потому что многие говорят что я могу так
but they begin to justify Well, yes, the
но они начинают обосновывать Ну да мышь
mouse is also NATO bases white laboratory,
там тоже базы НАТО белая лаборатории вся
all this garbage begins The first one does not
вот эта [__] начинается Первое не
support  the second is to
поддерживает второе по максимуму
sabotage the
саботировать
mobilization of
мобилизации
debilitation to the maximum and so on 3 you can
дебилизации и так далее 3 можно влиять
influence everything but your circle of friends, no
на все но на свой круг общения как бы
matter how it is, but the relatives behind the
там ни было но вот родственники за
zombified are not zombified, but still
зомбированы не зазомбирован но всё равно
it reprograms,
оно перепрограммирует
see Circle anyway people change
смотри Круг все равно люди меняются
water wears away stone Yes Circle of people Yes but
вода камень точит Да Круг людей Да а
then she heard heard heard and
потом вот она слышала слышала Слышал а
then it is superimposed for a year On the situation
потом он год накладывается На ситуацию
Because now the
Потому что сейчас пока еще
Russian troops are still kept there in Ukraine
российские войска там держится в Украине
so it is not perceived that way
так оно не так воспринимается А когда их
look to another
оно уже будет совсем по-другому смотреть
and mom will say oh, but what do
и мама скажет ой а что же
you understand what is now, that's exactly
Сами понимаете то что сейчас вот именно
what Russia is experiencing now  it’s just that I don’t
что сейчас Россия испытывает Просто я не
know complete complete [ __ ] up
знаю полный полный [__]
it’s just that I don’t know Putin is trying to
это просто я не знаю Путин пытается
leave a face, only the only thing he
оставить лицо только единственное ему
needs to somehow leave Ukraine is
надо как-то уйти из Украины
not to crap already it’s clear everything already everyone
не обосраться уже понятно все уже все
already understands this and in business this is how it
уже понимает это и по делам это так и
should be
должно быть
I see that here are yours  to
я смотрю что вот ваших этих там
throw them on there now, Ukraine will freeze
накидывать вот сейчас Украина замерзнет
and surrender to Ukraine, that is, on an internal
и сдаст Украины то есть на внутреннюю
trip they are somehow throwing something like
поездку как-то накидывают что типа
Russia hasn’t crap, just now
Россия не обосралась вот сейчас еще
Wait another two or three weeks there,
Подождите еще там две-три недельки
two or three weeks, they feed the
две-три недельки вот этим кормят
population on the inner surface with this
население на внутреннюю поверхность
Well, our people are all-  that's
Ну наши люди все-таки так думают Вот
exactly what the locals think it's
именно местные думают что
[ __ ], you see, here they go,
охреневая Понимаете вот они едут вот эти
these fools, that's right, it's real, that is, it
вот дурни вот прям вот реально То есть
turns out not to go according to the agenda, it's a
получается не пойти по повестке это
fine from 500 to 3,000 rubles, just
штраф от 500 до 3000 рублей просто
the same [ __ ] here they just go stupidly to the
эти же [__] вот они просто идут тупо на
slaughter, sit thumping spirit flakes  dill and
убой сидят бухает духа хлопья укропов и
sit in the car [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] cattle I
сидят в машину [__] [__] ебаная [__] Я
don’t know
не знаю
they don’t do it at home
они дома ни хрена не делает
when a person doesn’t have
это когда у человека вообще нету ничего
anything happening at all, at least she
не происходящего хотя бы
also watched that  what kind of psychology he sits
тоже смотрел такую психологию он сидит
He is nobody at home a nonentity at work a
Он никто он дома [__] на работе
nonentity here he is now making history there is
ничтожества тут он сейчас там вершит
shorter than the fate of an
историю короче там судьбы
egregor and you can just
эгрегору и можно здесь как раз
work
отработать
it out here Okay well thank you for the conversations
это Окей хорошо спасибо вам за разговоры
it was a little distracting in my soul But I
тяж так на душе немножко отвлекло Но я
think that all the same we must not  give
считаю что все-таки надо не опускать
up And talk to people because,
руки А с людьми говорить потому что
let's say,
скажем
everything changes like this and the human brain is
все меняется так и человеческий мозг Он
also not a stone Yes, it is difficult to
тоже не камень Да его трудно
reprogram it Because it was
перепрограммировать Потому что его
inflated pumped from all sides But
накачивали накачивали со всех сторон Но
this must be done
это надо делать
sometimes, you understand, not a stone is not a stone, but
иногда понимаете не камень не камень но
most likely this human brain
скорее всего вот этот человеческий мозг
which is now  that's it, this
которого сейчас вот именно вот этот
wadded Russian one needs it right, very
ватный российский его нужно прям очень
tough, you already understand, just take a
жестко уже понимаете прям брать
puncher and work harder to
перфоратор и больше работать
sharpen the stone already. It seems to me that it
камень точить уже Мне кажется здесь не
won’t work here, you need every little bit with a
получится вот надо каждый немножечко
puncher.
перфоратором
Yes, a teak character,
Да тиковой персонаж
what can I say?
что я скажу я абсолютно назвать русский
I believe that nothing can be
слышит я не верю в то что ничего нельзя
done, nothing can ever be
сделать никак нельзя изменить всегда
changed  Yes, you can change people’s thinking,
всегда можно изменить мышление людей
always just say when I’m a
всегда просто скажем когда вот я
small child His thinking is easier to change
маленький ребенок Его мышление изменить
because he doesn’t have attitudes yet,
проще потому что у него еще нет
it’s less intensely
установок это менее усиленно
an adult formed person, it’s
взрослого сформированного человека
more difficult to change attitudes, but it changes, and
сложнее меняется установки но меняется и
90 percent of those who are now dying for
90 процентов этих кто сейчас намрет за
them can be changed 10 Yes, they will be stubborn
их можно поменять 10 Да будут упоротами
that
что
there won’t be enough time for life resources
не хватит времена жизненных ресурсов
to change them, but it’s not worth the question of
чтобы их поменять но и не стоит вопрос
everyone, you need the majority, you need to move the
всех нужно большинство нужно двигать
thought of the majority in the right direction and
мысль большинства в правильное русло и
therefore don’t stop even one
поэтому не останавливайтесь даже один
person with whom you talk
человек с которым вы Поговорите
to talk regularly, so at school the
регулярно поговорить так вот в школе
teacher says he is younger
общение идет учитель говорит он младших
or in kindergarten  children to my pens because
или в садике дети моим ручки потому что
there are microbes children to my pens because
там микробы дети моим ручки потому что
there are microbes and damn it there 30 40 someone
там микробы и блин на там 30 40 кто-то
will start washing their hands in two times, someone
через два раза начнет мыть ручки кто-то
in 10 And someone will start washing in three months
через 10 А кто-то через три месяца
hands we are all adults my
начнет мыть руки мы все взрослые мои
hands taught us before eating in my opinion
руки нас научили перед едой по моему
everything can be
все можно
reprogrammed but yes it is necessary
перепрограммировать но да надо
make an effort What do
прикладывать к этому усилия Что вы
you guys want all
хотите ребята все
[music]
[музыка]
Well, like this is a type of war In short, we don’t
Ну типа это война типа Все короче не
support But exactly thank you for saying
поддерживаем А точно спасибо что сказал
No, it’s hard
Нет это тяжело
and for whom it’s easy now for people who are fighting
а кому сейчас легко людям которые воюют
against the Russian Federation there now in the
против Российской Федерации там сейчас в
trenches it’s easy
окопах им что легко
for them so don’t  to tell that
так что не надо рассказывать что
it’s impossible to reprogram this water,
нельзя перепрограммировать это вода ко
we definitely take everything to me and everyone
мне точно все берем и работает каждый
who can think that I can at least a
кто что может подумать что я могу хоть
little bit advance so at least a drop of a
чуть-чуть продвинуть так хоть капельку
bulging brain is a person and we
выгристого мозга человек и грызем грызем
gnaw gnaw gnaw if you can’t gnaw yourself at
грызем если не можете сами грызть хотя
least support such videos
бы поддержите вот такие видео
spread
распространяйте
comment to  didn’t take off to the top
комментируйте чтобы не взлетали в топ
anyway, some people will look, someone will
все равно какие-то люди посмотрят кто-то
think, here a lot of people write to me
задумается вот ко мне очень много людей
in a personal message that it’s so Andrey, while
пишет в личку что таки так Андрей я вот
watching your video I
смотря ваше видео
changed my mind about This is mine
изменил мнение про Вот это своего
At first I somehow
Сначала я как-то
supported it now 50/50  I have already
50 на 50 поддерживал это сейчас мне уже
clearly formed an opinion
однозначно четко сформировалось мнение
watching your videos. So
просмотр ваших видео Так что
this is wrong because someone was
это неправильно потому что кто-то было
intoxicated by the Minsk agreements  someone
дурманен минскими соглашениями кто-то
else was something else thinks that Ukraine
ещё был чем-то думает что Украина
is to blame Ukraine when we analyze we
виновата Украина когда мы Разбираем мы
look everything changes for someone faster for
смотрим всё меняет у кого-то быстрее у
someone more difficult so don’t sit idly
кого-то сложнее поэтому не сидите сложа
by and think How can you change even a
руки а думайте Как можно менять даже
small drop here a drop a drop a
маленькая капля вот капелька капелька
drop And then  this Chan is gaining and
капелька А потом этот Чан набирается и
everything and overflowing through
все и переливается через
do not sit Fold your hands and think what you can
не сидите Сложи руки а думайте что можно
do and do And although small
сделать и делать И хотя маленькие